68 Lake St. APT#101 White Plains, New York 10603 | Phone: (312)375-5363 | E-mail: xusufairy@gmail.com

SUMMARY

MBA candidate in Financial Markets and Risk Management. Broad and intense coursework and internship experience in finance / economic / accounting fields. Strong skills in data analysis, risk assessment & management, accounting records preparation, examination and analysis.

EDUCATION

University of Illinois at Chicago

Chicago, IL

Corporate Master in Business Administration

August 2013

GPA: 3.22/4.00

Northeast Forestry University

Harbin, China

Bachelor of Economics and Management in International Economics and Trade

July 2011

Harbin University of Science and Technology

Harbin, China

Bachelor of Economics in Finance of Economics (minor)

July 2011

EXPERIENCE

Administrative Assistant in Data Operation Department

Dec 2010 – Feb 2011

Starlaser Electronics Co., Ltd.

- Combined with practical operation of international data transforming affairs;
- Took charge of medical policy proofreading at some hospitals of Kansas State.

Manager Assistant in Investment Department

Jul 2010 – Aug 2010

China Construction Bank Harbin Branch

- Took charge of routine consultation and explanation to customers;
- Provided summary report of customer demand for Marketing Department;
- Prepared data analysis report of monthly investment profit;
- Made summary presentation on the stage weekly.

Intern in Marketing Department

Jan 2009 - Mar 2009

China Galaxy Securities Co., Ltd.

- Introduced the service contents and advantages of bank cards for new customers;
- Provided customer & market analysis report to the manager;
- Checked customers' personal information; singed and issued bank credit cards to customers

Educational Internship

Jun 2008 – Feb 2009

Northeast Forestry University

- Targeted at computer application and practical operation of international trade affairs;
- Conducted concrete operations in the computer room of School of Economics and Management in Northeast Forestry University.

VOLUNTEER

| Vol | unteer in | HUST | in | Harbin | 24th | Winter | Univers | idad |
|-------------------------|-----------|------|----|--------|------|--------|---------|------|
|-------------------------|-----------|------|----|--------|------|--------|---------|------|

Mar 2009

• No. 190 Torch Bearer of Harbin Stop in Beijing 2008 Olympic Games Torch Relay

Jul 2008

• Heilongjiang Association - Wenchuan 512 Earthquake Donation Association Supervisor

May 2008

SKILLS

- Software: Strong knowledge and experience in Microsoft Office Suite, Adobe Photoshop.
- Language: English, Mandarin Chinese.